jabong.com 2019-12-31

# Wear your style: Jabong.com

 about jabong 

about jabong 

 contact 

contact

 privacy policy 

## Privacy Policy

### 1\. Data Privacy Policy

1.1. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) shall form an integral part of the Terms of Use of the Website (“Terms”) and shall be read along with the Terms. Any capitalized term not specifically defined herein shall draw its meaning from the meaning ascribed to such term in the Terms.

1.2. We are Jade eServices Private Limited from, Gurgaon, Haryana, India – 122015, owner of Jabong.com, and a group entity of Myntra Designs Private Limited situated at Bangalore. In this Privacy Policy, references to “you” and “User” mean any person submitting any data to us or our agent or the Website. The Website is operated by Myntra Designs Private Limited., a company incorporated under the laws of India having its registered office in Bangalore. All references to Website in these Terms shall deem to refer to the aforesaid entity in inclusion of the online portal.

1.3. If you have any comments or suggestions, we would be pleased to receive them at our Gurgaon address or at our email address, [care@jabong.com](mailto:care@jabong.com)

1.4. We view protection of Your privacy as a very important principle. We understand clearly that You and Your Personal Information is one of Our most important assets. We store and process Your Information including any sensitive financial information collected as defined under the Information Technology Act, 2000 and Rules there under. We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates.

1.5. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

1.6. We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. We have developed this Privacy Policy to protect Your personal/financial information and keep it confidential. By visiting Our Jabong, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policies. The following Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy outlines the information we may process and how we may use that information to better serve you while using our Jabong.

1.7. **Correspondence Information**. Following are the various Correspondence Information which You provide when You access/register for Our Service includes:

  * Children under the age of 18: Use of the Platform is available only to persons who can form legally binding contracts under Indian Contract Act, 1872. Persons who are "incompetent to contract" within the meaning of the Indian Contract Act, 1872 including minors, un-discharged insolvents etc. are not eligible to use the Platform. If you are a minor i.e. under the age of 18 years, you shall not register as a User of the Platform and shall not transact on or use the Platform. As a minor if you wish to use or transact on Jabong, such use or transaction may be made by your legal guardian or parents on the Platform. 
  * Personal Information: name, gender, age, images, contact/ postal address, telephone, email id, nationality and content. 
  * Financial Information: credit/ debit card details including card number and expiry date in encrypted form, details for net banking services and Wallet services. Please be advised that Jabong ensures the highest degree of data security, while encrypting as per the guidelines specified by _Payment Cards Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)_. 
  * Payment and Account Information: Your account history with us including (without limitation) all billing information and communications, payment history etc. We maintain this in encrypted form on secure servers. However, your transactions details may be preserved by Jabong for purposes of tax or regulatory compliance. 
  * Transactional Information: Order ID, transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities on our Jabong. 
  * User IDs: Your usernames, passwords, email addresses, contacts, account including third-party accounts and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services. 
  * Stored Information: Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc. 
  * Shared Information: What types of information are not allowed on Platform? 
  * Nudity or other sexually suggestive content 
  * Hate speech, credible threats or direct attacks on an individual or group 
  * Content that contains self-harm or excessive violence 
  * Fake or impostor profiles 
  * Spam

1.8. **Technical and functional management of the Platform.** When you use our Platform, we also process technical data such as your IP-address, Device ID, Device Contacts, Device Accounts including third-party accounts or MAC-address, and information about the manufacturer, model, and operating system of your mobile device. We use this data to enable us to deliver the functionalities of the Platform, resolve technical difficulties, and provide you with the correct (prevent the transmission of spam, viruses and/or unlawful, defamatory, obscene or otherwise undesirable material or content) and most up to date version of the Platform.

  * **Operational Use**. We may use your information for suggesting products and promotional offers and schemes. You may update your profiling information at any time on the Platform. You acknowledge and agree such update is for Your interests and for improving personalization and service efficiency of the Platform. 

**Note: You acknowledge that, we will only disclose your information in an aggregated form which is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you.**

  * **Applicable law and procedure**. We collect and store your Correspondence Information to: (a) comply with our obligations under law and (b) monitor your use of our Services in order to ensure your compliance with our Terms of Service. 

**Note: However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Any transmission of information by you to our Platform is at your own risk. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone.**

  * **Cookie Policy**. A cookie is a small text file that we place on your mobile device to enable various features of Jabong. "Cookies" are used to store user preferences and to track user trends, so as to enhance your interactive experience and generally improve our Services to you. You can change your cookie settings to accept or not accept cookies in your browser settings. If you do accept a "cookie", you thereby agree to our use of any Personal Information collected by us using that Cookie. If you do accept a "cookie", you thereby agree to our use of any Personal Information collected by us using that Cookie.Whenever Jabong uses a third party to host and serve content, we may arrange for a common identifier to be shared between the third party and Jabong in order to enable accurate measurement of traffic and usage. This includes but is not limited to the use of AMP Client IDs in Google Analytics for Accelerated Mobile Pages served by Google on Jabong's behalf.
  * **Third Party**. At times We may tie-up with third parties, brand owners or other partners and make available certain offers, events or special schemes. In such instances, Your personal information may be shared with such third parties and/or may become available to them or be disclosed to them, such third parties may have their own applicable privacy rules and We shall not be liable for the use or misuse of Your information by such third parties. 

**We only collect your Personal Information to conduct our business and to enable us to deliver and improve our services. We do not for any reason whatsoever sell your Correspondence Information to any third party or otherwise trade on it.**

1.9. You can visit the Website and browse without having to provide personal details. During your visit to the Website you remain anonymous and at no time can we identify you unless you have an account on the Website and log on with your user name and password.

1.10. We may collect various information if you seek to place an order for a product to us on the Website.

1.11. We collect, store and process your data for processing your purchase on the Website and any possible later claims, and to provide you with our services. We may collect your title, name, gender, email address, postal address, delivery address (if different), telephone number, mobile number, fax number, payment details, payment card details or bank account details, Internet protocol(IP) address, personal information received from social networking sites through which the You have registered to the Website including name, profile picture, email address or friends list, and any information made public in connection with that social media service and such other personal and non-personal information that may be required to access and operate the Website.

1.12. Please be advised that the duration of use of the Website by You may also be logged and stored by the Website.

1.13. The information may be collected and/or stored in electronic form, however, we are hereby authorized by You to collect/store such information is physical form as well.

1.14. We need this information in order to allow you to go ahead with placing your order for a product. We may use that data to process payment for the product and deliver the product to you. We also use that data to inform you when the product is about to be delivered.

1.15. We may share the information collected from You with our affiliates, employees, agents, service provider, sellers, suppliers, banks, payment gateway operators and such other individuals and institutions like judicial, quasi-judicial law enforcement agencies. Our affiliates may market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-out.

1.16. We may pass your name and address on to a third party in order to make delivery of the product to you (for example to our courier or supplier).

1.17. We may also use your data in order to manage the Website, collect payment from you, enable you to subsequently use parts of the Website, detect any fraud or Website abuses, send you information relevant to the Website or our products, and in case we have any queries. Payments that you make through the Website will be processed by Myntra Designs Private Limited, a company registered in India.

1.18. You shall indemnify and hold harmless the Website and each of the Website’s officers, directors, contracts or agents and any third party relying on the information provided by You in the event You are in breach of this Policy.

1.19. Your actual order details may also be stored with us and you may access this information by logging into your account on the Website. Here you can view the details of your orders that have been completed, those which are open and those which are shortly to be dispatched and administer your address details, bank details and any newsletter to which you may have subscribed. You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault.

1.20. We shall not share any of your personal information with third parties without your explicit consent. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent and we only use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. We view protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and Your information is one of our most important assets. We store and process Your information on computers located in the India that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. We use third parties to verify and certify our privacy principles. If you object to your information being transferred or used in this way please do not use the Website.

1.21. Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your personal information that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

1.22. WNotwithstanding anything to the contrary, the Website shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of the information provided by You.

1.23. When you download or use Jabong mobile apps, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. You can also turn off the location services using your mobile phone settings.

 terms and conditions 

terms and conditions

 vendors code of conduct 

vendors code of conduct

 Offers Terms and Conditions 

Offers Terms and Conditions
